ADVENTURE towering above the majestic Rockies!
Green Grass of Wyoming is a drama, family, western film directed by Louis King.
The romance of a rancher's niece and a rival rancher's son
parallels that of a stallion and a mare.
Carey Greenway, played by Peggy Cummins.
Beaver Greenway, played by Charles Coburn.
Ken McLaughlin, played by Robert Arthur.
Rob McLaughlin, played by Lloyd Nolan.
Gus, played by Burl Ives.
Nell McLaughlin, played by Geraldine Wall.
Green Grass of Wyoming is a 1948 American Western film directed by Louis King
and starring Peggy Cummins, Charles Coburn and Robert Arthur.
The screenplay, written by Martin Berkeley, is based on the third book in the
popular, "My Friend Flicka" trilogy, written by Mary O'Hara.
The film follows the further adventures of the McLaughlin
family who live on a horse ranch in Wyoming.
Marilyn Monroe appeared as an uncredited extra.
The original cast from the first two films did not
reprise their roles in the third.
The film explores themes of horse, ranch, romance.
The tone is emotional.